The only thing deadlier than a serial killer... is a cop with a license to kill.
Officer Down is a tv movie, thriller, crime film directed by Christopher Miller.
A policewoman unwittingly puts her family in danger when
she uncovers corruption in her department.
Detective Kathryn Shaunessy, played by Sherilyn Fenn.
Officer Philip Hallows, played by Casper Van Dien.
Detective Gary Hill, played by Jerry Kroll.
Captain Raymond Taggart, played by Larry Drake.
Commissioner Donald Hallows, played by Ted Shackelford.
Bates, played by Joe Ochman.
Hostage is a 2005 American action thriller film directed by
Florent Siri from the screenplay by Doug Richardson.
It is based on the 2001 novel of the same name by Robert Crais.
The film stars Bruce Willis, Kevin Pollak, Ben Foster, and Jonathan Tucker and follows the police chief who takes
place as the negotiator when the family of a wealthy accountant is held hostage by three teenagers.
Hostage was released in the United States on March 11, 2005, by Miramax Films.
It received mixed reviews from critics, and was a box-office disappointment,
grossing $78 million worldwide on a budget of $75 million.
The tone is intense.